Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1974-2002; 9; 32.51 cubic ft.
  - Allows the Division of Lottery to Conduct Investigations of Sales Agents and Applicants, 1995 (Box 26 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Extends the Community Services Block Grant Program, 1995 (Box 26 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Allows the Transfer of Monies without an Appropriation by Law, 1995 (Box 26 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - Long Term Borrowing Practices Reform and Long Term Debt Reform Proposal, 1995 (Box 26 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - Allows ORDA to Operate the 1932 and 1980 Lake Placid Winter Olympic Museum, 1995 (Box 26 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - Creation of the Lake Placid Olympic Training Fund and Special Vanity Plates, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Triennial Explosives License Procedures, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Review of the Consensus Revenue Forecast by the Comptroller, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Johnsburg easement to ORDA, Gore Mountain, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Legislative Resolution Urging Congress to Remedy Acid Rain, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Legislative Resolution Mourning the Death of Firefighter P. MacMurray of Hudson Falls Volunteer Fire Department, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Legislative Resolution Mourning the Death of Former Assemblyman, Judge Sheldon Fow Wickes, Distinguished Citizen and Philanthropist, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Resolution Mourning the Death of William C. Ross, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Legislative Resolution Paying Tribute to Technical Sergeant R. Sayward of the United States Air Force upon the Occasion of his Designation for Special Honor for Distinguished Community Service, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Resolution Congratulating the Bells on their 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Resolution Honoring B. Kelly upon the occasion of her designation for Special Honor, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Resolution Honoring Father W. Esmond upon the occasion of the 40th Anniversary of his Ordination, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Creation of the State and Local Government Short-Term Investment Pool, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Vendor Responsibility and Disqualification, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Pistol Permit for Out of State Residents, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - State Government Performance Accountability Act, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Comptroller Subpoena Power, Access to Certain Information, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Volunteer Fire Departments and Ambulance Motor Fuel Tax Exemption, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Cancer Screenings, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 19-22)
  - Tourism in the Adirondacks, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Legislative Resolution Congratulating the Repas Upon the Occasion of their 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending W. McBride, President and Owner of Bill McBride Chevrolet, Inc. of Plattsburgh upon the designation as recipient of the 1995 Time Quality Dealer Award (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Notaries Public, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Plattsburgh Highways, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Sagamore Institute Bridges, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Installment of Bond to Finance the Transportation of Solid Waste in Long Lake, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Establishment of an Ovarian Cancer Information Program, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Purchase of New County Road Machinery, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - HIV Testing, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Legislative Resolution Commemorating the 2nd Annual Essex Maritime Festival, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending C. Gellar Kolchetski upon the occasion of her retirement after 48 years of dedicated service to the State of New York, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending M. McCurry of Queensbury School District in Recognition of her 41 years of Outstanding Service, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending the Wilmington E.M. Cooper Memorial Public Library upon the presentation of its Absolute Charter by the New York State Board of Regent, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Authorizes the Town of Danemora to Discontinue Certain Parklands, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Authorizes the State to Invest in Obligation of United States Agencies, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Allows the Comptroller to Sell Bonds, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending D. Doyle upon the occasion of his retirement following a distinguished career of 27 years with the State University of New York, Plattsburgh, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Legislative Resolution Commemorating the 130th Anniversary of Finch, Pruyn and Company, Inc., 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Zoning in the Town of Kingsbury, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Beer Wholesale, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Licenses to Sell Beer and Wine, 1995 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Saranac Inn Exchange of Certain Forest Lands, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Legislative Resolution Commending M. Lavery, Director of SUNY Plattsburgh's Alumni Affairs, Upon the Occasion of his Retirement after 24 years of Dedicated Service, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Legislative Resolution Mourning the Death of W. Murphy, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Allows Ticonderoga to Lease Parklands, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Publicity Fun for the Town of Wilmington, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Distribution of Additional Mortgage Recordings, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Supplemental Police Service to Towns and Villages, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Washington County and New York State Highway Transfer, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - Relates to Payment of Fees and Other Charges by Credit Cards, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - 1932 and 1980 Winter Olympic Museum within the Olympic Regional Development Authority, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - L. Strait Tier I Retirement Status, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Allows State Agencies to Accept Credit Cards, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Exemption of "Shopping Papers" from Sales Tax, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Confirming Certain Acts of Various Boards in Kingsbury, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 58-59)
  - Allow Washington County to Spend Tax Proceeds on Community Colleges, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - No Time Barred on Causes of Action for Agent Orange, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Prohibit the Adirondack Park Agency from Directing Removal of a Non-Conforming, Man-Made Structure that's been in the Park for 10 or more years, 1996 (Box 27 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Approval Declaration for Act Authorizing Willsboro to Covey Land No Longer Needed for Park Purposes, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Resolution, Commending Joseph Peter Whellock Upon the Occasion of his ordination to the Roman Catholic Priesthood on Saturday May 25, 1996 by Ogdensburg Diocese Bishop Paul S. Loverde (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Legislative Resolution, Commending Sigurd Rascher upon the occasion of his designation as recipient of the "Edwin Franko Goldman Memorial Citation" by the American Bandmasters Association, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Legislative Resolution congratulating the Westport High School Girls Varsity Basketball Team and Coach Tom Beauvais on their outstanding season and overall team record, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly proposing amendments to Sections 6, 13, 14, and 16 of Article 3, Section 7 of Article 4 and Sections 3, 4, and 5 of Article 7 of the Constitution, in relation to implementing the budge of the previous fiscal, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Conveyance of Certain Real Property to D. Cleveland by New York State Thruway Authority, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - An Act Approving the Exchange of Certain Lands Between the Town of Keene and the people of the State of New York, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in relation to Franchise Taxation of Thrift Reserves for Loan Losses, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Bear Management Bill, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Continued Existence of Hamilton County Industrial Development Agency for Ten More Years, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, in relation to the New York State Deferred Compensation Board, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, in relation to the creation of a Debt Management Board and limiting the amount of state related debt that may be issued, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, in relation to late water, sewer, refuse collection and/or disposal payments, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - An Act to Amend the State Finance Law, in relation to court facilities, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - An Act to Amend the Railroad Law, in relation to Jurisdiction of Railroad Police Officers, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - An Act to Legalize, Ratify and Confirm the Acts and Proceedings of the Board of Education of the Johnsburg Central School District at North Creek, Warren County, in Relation to a purchase of a school bus and to authorize the Commissioner of Education to p, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - An Act Legalizing and Validating the Expenditure of Certain Bond Anticipation Note and Serial Bond proceeds of the Saranac Central School District, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Health Law, in relation to Descheduling Fenfluramine and its salts and isomers, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in relation to Solicitation and Collection of Charitable Contributions, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly proposing amendments to Article 7 of the Constitution, in relation to the prohibition of certain borrowing arrangements, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - An Act in relation to the employment status of J. Helmer, a member of the New York State and Local Employees' Retirement System, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Establishment of the Welfare Fraud Control Unit within the Department of Law Enforcement, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Authorizing the Village of Whitehall to convey certain land no longer needed for park purposes, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Legislative Resolution congratulating the Franklin Academy Girls Varsity Basketball Team and Coach Mike Wescott on their outstanding season and overall team record, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Legislative Resolution commemorating the 100th Anniversary of the Sylvan Star Chapter #122, Order of the Eastern Star in Granville, New York, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Resolution commemorating the All-American Picnic to be hosted by the Great Escape Fun Park, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Legislative Resolution commemorating the life and career of Father Isaac Joques, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - An Act to Amend the State Law and the State Finance Law, in relation to the Marketing and Sale of Memorabilia representing the State's Heritage and History, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - An Act to Legalize, Ratify and Confirm the Acts and Proceedings of the Board of Education of the Johnsburg Central School District at North Creek, Warren County, in Relation to a purchase of a school bus, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Legislative Resolution commemorating the 200th Anniversary of Granville Lodge #55, Free and Accepted Masons, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, in relation to the date local governments may opt-in to the retirement plan for certain sheriffs, undersheriffs, deputy sheriffs, and correction offices, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Forest Fire Suppression in Adirondack Park, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Authorizing the Town of Willsboro to convey certain land no longer needed for park purposes, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Legislative Resolution Paying Tribute to the Life and Accomplishments of J. Wyrtzen, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Legislative Resolution honoring the students of Glens Falls Middle School in Recognition of their Efforts to raise $20,000 in a Campaign to Fight the Destructive Effects of Acid Rain on their Adirondack Community, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly proposing amendments to sections 1, 2, 11, and 12 of Article 7 of the Constitution, in relation to the submission of a capital program and financing plan and the number of ballot propositions authorizing de, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in relation to the Electronic Funds Transfer Program and to repeal certain provisions of such law relating thereto, 1996 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Explosives License, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Advertising in the Adirondack Park (Kiosks), 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Management and Taking of Bear, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - County Responsibility for Forest Fire Expenses, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Abolishing the Coyote Hunting Permit Requirement, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Extends Legislation Allowing Secretary of State to Accept Credit Cards for Payment, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Bolton Central School District School Bus Bill, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Increasing the Criminal Penalties for Illegally Taking Big Game, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Abandonment of Certain Town Highways, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Non-Hazardous Municipal Landfill Closures, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Requirement for School Bus Headlights to be Illuminated wile in Operation, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Prohibiting Abandonment of Crane Pond Road in the Town of Schroon, Essex County, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Power of Initiative, Indirect Initiative, and Referendum for Electors, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - An Act in relation to granting Tier 1 Retirement Status to certain public employees, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - An Act to Amend the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, in relation to the Terms of Sale on Beer and Wine Products Purchased for Resale for on or off premises consumption and the fee to be paid for a license to sell alcoholic beverages for on premises consump, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Creating a Revolving Loan Program for State Assistance to Municipalities for the Environmental Restoration of Certain Sites for Specific Industrial or Commercial Uses, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in relation to the Presumptive Minimum Sales Price of Cigarettes with the State, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 53-54)
  - Mobile Instructional Units, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Personal Income Tax Credit for Qualified Adoption Expenses, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Authorizes J. A. Berkley Hose Company No. 1 to build and operate a Firehouse Outside of Argyle, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Tax Refunds or Credits for Omnibus Carriers, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - Legalizing and Validating the Expenditure of Certain Bonds and Proceeds of Saranac Central School District, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - L. Strait Tier I Retirement Status, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - Consolidation of the Separate Capital Plan Reports, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - New Limitations on Legislature's Ability to Raise Taxes and Fees, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Requires Multi-Year Budget Planning and Establishment of Cash-Based Budgeting, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Private Forest Land Assessment and State Assistance, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - The Patient Care Improvement Act, 1997 (Box 28 (9-Legislation), Folder 65-66)
  - Lien Law in Relation to the Duration of Mechanics' Liens, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Unclassified vs. Classified Service in the SUNY System, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Providing a Family Court Judge in Clinton County, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Electric Funds Transfer (Alcoholic Beverage Tax), 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Carrying a Pistol or Revolver While Hunting Deer During Archery or Muzzle-Loading Seasons, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - "Contract" Policing by the State Police, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Electronic Value Transfer Devices and Credit Cards, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Schroon Lake Water District Change, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Coin Telephone Tax, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Inclusion of Indian Children in Salmon River Central School District Enrollment, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Transportation Mobility Revolving Loan Fund, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Allow members of the NYPD to be the Commissioner's Representative at Meetings, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Indemnification of Employees of the New York State Environmental Facilities Corporation, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Essex County Real Estate Transfer Tax, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - St. Armand Fire District Boundaries, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Definition of "Medical Necessity", 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 16-17)
  - Jurisdiction of State Ethics Commission over former state employees, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Jurisdiction of Land Comprising the Federal Correctional Institution at Ray Brook, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Retirement of D. LaBelle, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Procurement of Contracts Greater than $100,000, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Extension of the Metropolitan Transportation Business Tax Surcharge, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Definition of "State Agency", 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Technical Amendments to Public Officers' Law, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Permitting the Secretary of State to Receive Electronic Records, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Change in Deadline for Filing List of Policy-Makers, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Changes in Procurement Stewardship Act, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Indemnification by Members of the Dormitory Authority, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Size of Maps Filed in Clinton County, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Non-Hazardous Municipal Landfill Closure, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Retirement Benefits for the Widow of B. Bourgeois, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Authorizes a Voluntary Administration to Discharge a Mortgage, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Standardizing and Improving State Agency Permit Applications, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Deferred Compensation, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Mortgage Recording Tax in Franklin County, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Lowering the Minimum Balance Required for a Wagering Account, 1997 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Olympic Regional Development Authority and Johnsburg, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Eliminates Double Taxation on Dividends Tax, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Extensions for the Payment of Taxes in the Case of a State Disaster Emergency, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - An Act Amending the State Finance Law, in Relation to Establishing the Division of Parole Asset Forfeiture Fund, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Extension of Time for the Collection of Taxes, Fines, and Payments Owed to Government Agencies and Extension of Filing Deadlines for Applications and Reports to Government Agencies as a result of State Disaster Emergencies, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Sales Tax Exemption for Broadcasters, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - An Act to Amend Chapter 303 of the Laws of 1988, Relating to the Extension of the State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol, in Relation to Extending such Provisions for an Additional Five Years, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Allowing Minors to Possess Antique Firearms in Certain Cases, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - An Act to Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Signs, Displays, or Devices on State Highways, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - An Act to Amend Chapter 989 of the Laws of 1958, Relating to the Temporary State Commission of Investigation, in relation to Extending the Provisions of Such Chapter, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Offenders Law, in Relation to Gifts Offered to Gubernatorial Nominees whose Nominations are Pending Senate Confirmation, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to the Commission on Uniform State Laws, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - An Act to Amend Chapter 303 of the Laws of 1988, Relating to the Extension of the State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol, in Relation to Extending such Provisions for an Additional Five Years, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to the Information Available from the State Ethics Commission, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Permit Former State Officers or Employees to Contract with State Agencies where the Contractor has Expertise in a Particular Matter, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Officers Law and the Executive Law, in Relation to Business and Professional Activities by Covered Individuals and to the functions, powers and duties of the State Ethics Commission, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - Authorize Saranac Lake to Discontinue the Use of and Convey Certain Park Lands, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to the Dairy Indemnity Program and Providing for the Repeal of such Provisions upon expiration thereof, 1998 (Box 29 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)